Guide to the League of Women Voters of the Fairfax Area records, 1948-2009
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 5: Conventions and Meetings, 1965-2008; (2.5 boxes)
  Series 5 contains information and publications pertaining to the League's meetings and conventions, including important events such as anniversary celebrations. The series is arranged chronologically in 2 boxes.
  - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Annual Meeting Arrangements, 1965-1998 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Annual: Convention/Meeting (Program summary minutes), 1968-1992 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Annual: Conv./Mtg. Program Summary, 1971-1998 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Convention, 1974-1987 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Annual Meeting, 1977-1996 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Annual: Conv./Mtg.-Big City/Large League, 1978-1996 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Annual Convention Arrangements, 1982-1991 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - National Capital Area Annual Convention Workbook, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - National Capital Area Convention Paperwork, 1987-1997 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - National Capital Area Annual Convention Workbook, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Annual Convention/Meetings Paperwork, 1988-2000 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - National Capital Area Annual Convention Workbook, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Reaching New Heights Convention, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - National Capital Area Annual Convention Workbook, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Convention, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - National Capital Area Annual Convention Workbook, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Making a Difference Convention Workbook, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Convention, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - National Capital Area Annual Convention Workbook, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Take Back the System: The Voters' Revolution Convention Workbook, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - National Capital Area Annual Convention Workbook, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Virginia Convention, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - National Capital Area Annual Convention Workbook, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Convention Workbook, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - National Capital Area Annual Convention Workbook, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - National Capital Area Annual Convention Workbook, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - National Capital Area Annual Convention Workbook, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - National Capital Area Annual Convention Workbook, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Convention Paperwork, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - LWVUS 43rd National Convention Workbook, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - 50th Anniversary Gala, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - "Remember the Ladies", 2001 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - 45th Biennial Convention, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - LWVFA 60th Anniversary, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Series 6: Subject Files, 1953-2006; 29 boxes
  Series 6 contains the miscellaneous files of the League, including voting guides and other actions undertaken by the League. The series is arranged alphabetically in 29 boxes.
  - 75 Anniversary Membership Kit, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Action, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Action, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Action, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Action, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Action, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Action, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Action, 1984-1987 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Action, 1984-1987 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Action, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Action on Affordable Housing, 1966-1989 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Action Human Resources, 1964-1985 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Action Human Resources, 1964-1985 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Action on Land Use, 1973-1987 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Action on Land Use, 1973-1987 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Action on Land Use, 1973-1987 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Action-Local, 1989-1991 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - (Actions) Natural Resources Became Environmental Quality, 1978 - 1980 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - (Actions) Natural Resources Became Environmental Quality, 1969 - 1989 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - (Actions) Natural Resources Became Environmental Quality, 1977 - 1988 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Action Schools, 1970-1988 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Action Schools, 1970-1988 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Action Schools-Financing Education, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Action-Speeches, 1970s (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Action: System of Justice, mid 1970s-1988 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Action: System of Justice, mid 1970s-1988 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Action-Transportation Survey, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Advocacy/Round Table, 1991 - 1999 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Air Pollution-CAAA, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Amicus Brief-Rt. 28 Case, 1990-1991 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Annual: Conv./Meeting Kits, 1975-1985 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Annual: Meeting, 1959-1974 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Annual Meeting, 1975-1992 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Ballot Questions, 1974-1981 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Board and Off-Board Job Description, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Bookmarks, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Budget: Testimony, 1980-1983 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Bylaws, 1967 - 1993 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Bylaws, 1984 - 1987 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Candidates' Calendar, 1979 - 1984 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Candidates' Forum: Cities and Towns, 1968-1985 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Candidates' Forum: Congressional, 1974-1980 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Candidates' Forum: Special Election, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Candidates' Forum: Presidential, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Candidates' Forum-Statewide-House of Delegates, 1975-1977 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Candidates' Forum: Congressional, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Candidates' Forum: Special Election, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Carrie Chapman Catt: Founder, League of Women Voters, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Chesapeake Bay, 1984 - 1995 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Chesapeake Bay, 1990-1991 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Chesapeake Bay Conservation Awards, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Chesapeake Bay Presentation, 1992 - 1993 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Chevron Award Submission, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Chron. Action Taken at Federal Level, 1976 - 1992 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Chron Action Take by LWVFA at State Level, 1976 - 1993 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Citizen Participation, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - COG: Partnership for Regional Excellence, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - C and I Amicus Brief: Land Use, 1990-1991 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Commercial and Industrial Districts, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Commercial and Industrial Districts, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Community Cable T.V., 1981 - 1992 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Community: Chamber of Commerce, 1986 - 1992 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Community: Citizens for Balanced Growth Political Action Committee, 1991 - 1992 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Community: Fx. Co. Commission for Women, 1993 - 1994 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Community: General, 1979 - 1992 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Community LWVFA Awards, 1978 - 1993 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Consensus/Positions, 1984 - 1988 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Consensus Reports, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Construction Site Safety LWVFA Project (Channel 53), 1981 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Const. Officers FFx. Co. Voters Guide, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Construction Site Safety LWVFA Project (Interim and Final Project), 1981 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Construction Site Safety LWVFA Project (Panelists), 1980 - 1981 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Construction Site Safety LWVFA Project (Receipts), 1981 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Construction Site Safety LWVFA Project (VFH and P.P.), 1980 - 1981 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Construction Site Safety "Who Is Responsible?", 1981 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence Electoral Board and Registrar, 1967 - 1975 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Council-LWVVA, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - County Boards, Commissions, etc., 1987 - 1997 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Directories, 1985 - 1988 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Discussion Report, 1978 - 1992 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Documentation: Recycling Guides, 1990 - 1992 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Eat, Drink, and Vote! [recipes], 1968 - 1976 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Ecoloday, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Election Guide: Cities and Towns, 1965-1982 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Election Guide, 1974-1979 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Election Guide, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Election Guide, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Election Guide, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Election Guide, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Election Guide, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Election Guide: Congressional, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Election Guide, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Election Guide, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Election Guide, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Energy House Tours: Finance File, 1981 - 1983 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - EQ General, 1977 - 1987 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Equal Rights Amend. and Other VA Laws Primarily Affecting Women, 1973 - 1989 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Equal Rights Amendment-Action, 1977 - 1991 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Equal Rights Amendment-Action, 1974 - 1985 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Facts for Voters/Reports, 1984 - 1991 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Fairfax County Action, 1978 - 1984 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Fairfax Co. Background Info., 1977 - 1983 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Fairfax County Budget, 1953-1979 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Fairfax County Budget, 1980-1993 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Fairfax County Citizen of the Year, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Fairfax Co. Govt., 1973 - 1989 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Fairfax Chronicles, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Finance-Community Elections, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Finance: Community Elections Yorktown, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Finance Projects, 1973 - 1984 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Finance Units, 1986 - 1993 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Financial Disclosures by County Officials, 1984 - 1986 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Fiscal, 1973 - 1982 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Fiscal: Action, 1990 - 1995 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Fiscal: BOS testimony (non-budget), 1992 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Fiscal: EAC's Economic Strategic Plan, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Fiscal: Issues (BPOL), 1997 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Fiscal: Outside Audit Function, 1991 - 1993 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Park Dedication(s) [Joe Flackne], 1977 - 1992 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Park Dedication(s) [Joe Flackne], 1974 - 1994 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Tribute to Joe Flackne, 1961 - 1993 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Lorton Marker [Joe Flackne], 1980 - 1991 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Lorton Marker [Joe Flackne], 1974 - 1990 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Joe Flackne, 1989 - 1994 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Joe Flackne, 1961 - 1994 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Formation of Seperate Group Outside League to Study and Review Land Use Issues, 1986-1987 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Formation of Seperate Group Outside League to Study and Review Land Use Issues, 1986-1987 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Fundraising Projects, 1976 - 1982 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - General Meeting, 1996-1997 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - General V.S. Activities, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - General V.S. Activities, 1967-1979 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - General V.S. Activities, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - General V.S. Activities, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - General V.S. Activities, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - General V.S. Activities, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - General V.S. Activities, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - General V.S. Activities, 1989-1990 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Government Campaign, 1974 - 1998 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Governmental Center Fairfax County, 1986 - 1987 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Governor's Environmental Excellence Award, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Government: Issues: Local (Charter), 1977 - 1991 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Government: LWVFA Study Loc. Gov. Independent Program Auditor, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Growth Implications, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Guides-Distribution Lists, 1989 - 1991 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Health: Health Care Form, 1992 - 1994 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Historical Materials (Contributions/Proposal(s)/Charter), 1976 - 1995 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - House of Delegates Candidates, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Housing: Action, 1989 - 1995 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - HR: Mental Health, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Human Resources: Adult Domestic Violence, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - International Relations, 1977-1988 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - IR: Russian Interns Exchange Program, 1992 - 1993 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Items Removed For Preservation, 1962 - 1982 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Jailed for Freedom 1 of 3, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Jailed for Freedom 2 of 3, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Jailed for Freedom 3 of 3, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Jailed for Freedom Extras, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - J.C. Penney Golden Rule Award, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Justice: Action (Local), 1969 - 1971 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Justice: Action (Local), 1972 - 1986 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Land Use: Amicus Briefs, 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Land Use: Area Plans Review, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Land Use: FC Planning and Development Process, 1989 - 1991 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Land Use: Issues: Comprehensive Plan/Plan Review and Amendments, 1988 - 1992 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Land Use: Issues: Occoquan Down Zoning, 1978 - 1985 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Land Use: Issues: Occoquan Down Zoning, 1964 - 1984 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Land Use: Issues-State/National, 1973 - 1992 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Land Use (Local), 1978 - 1991 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Land Use: Recycling, 1991 - 1994 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Land Use: Rezoning in the Occoquan, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Land Use: Rt. 28, 1992 - 1993 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Land Use and Telecommunications, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Land Use: Transportation, 1990 - 1992 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Land Use: Tyson's Corner, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Land Use: Vesting, 1989 - 1992 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Land Use: Zonig Ord. Amend., 1994 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Land Use: ZO Amendment: Site Plans, 1994 - 1995 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - League of Women Voters Education Fund Get Out and Vote, 1984 - 1998 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - League Survey and Testimony For 1 Year on County Budget, 1986 - 1987 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Priorities for the General Assembly, 2001-2002 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Libraries, 1984 - 1993 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - List of LWVFA Members, 1976 - 1978 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Local Action, 1990s (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Local Govt. City Status, 1961-1962 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - LWVFA Advisory Committee, 1981 - 1991 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - LWVFA Concurrence Proposal, 1992 - 1993 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - LWVFA-Hist. File Lists, 1948 - 1969 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - LWVFA Testimony, 1964-1984 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - LWVFA Testimony, 1964-1989 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - LWVFA Testimony, 1964-1989 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Membership, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Membership: Development, 1977 - 1994 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Membership: Dues System, 1977 - 1993 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Membership: Exchange of Labels, 1991 - 1992 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Membership: Orientation, 1973 - 1990 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Membership: Profile, 1972 - 1994 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Membership: Recruitment, 1977 - 1994 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Membership Survey, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Membership Survey, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Membership Survey, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous File, 1976 - 1997 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Misc., 1960 - 2005 (Box 52, File 5)
  - Miscellaneous Materials, 1966 - 1995 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Pamphlets and Brochures, 1978 - 1995 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Money: All Finance Reports-NCA, 1987 - 1993 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Money-Audit Statement, 1986 - 1997 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Money: Finance/Correspondence, 1991 - 1997 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Money: Finance Ideas, 1975 - 1992 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Money: Grants, 1974 - 1987 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Money: Projects, 1973 - 1975 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Motor Voter, 1992 - 1993 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Nat'l Capital Area, 1967 - 1980 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Nat'l and Local Program Ping, 1949 - 1969 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - The Nationl Women's Hall of Fame, 1995 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Naturalization, 1970 - 1975 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - NCA: Drug Study, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - New Member Handbook/Brochure, 1999 - 2003 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - The Nineteenth Amendment, Undated (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Nomination for Chevron Environmental Award, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - N,VA Delegation, 1975 - 1999 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Natural Resources: Action-Water, 1990 - 1996 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Natural Resources: CQ-Compressed Natural Gas, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Natural Resources, 1986 - 1992 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Natural Resources-Early Recycling/Bottle Bill, 1972-1988 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Natural Resources: E.Q. Tree, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Natural Resource: Issues, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Natural Resources: Issues-Air Quality, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - N.R.: Issues-Challenge of the Clean, 1993 - 1994 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - N.R. Recycling Guide, 1989-1991 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Natural Resources: Stormwater Utilities, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Natural Resources: Underground Utility, 1995 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Occoquan Marker: Items Removed for Preservation, 1983 - 1987 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Photos and Correspondence, 1983 - 1995 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    Printouts of photos
  - Occoquan Marker: Media Reports and Clippings and Suffrage Log Copy, 1953 - 1983 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Occoquan Marker-Draft Report and Park Serv. Correspondence, 1982 - 1987 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Occoquan Marker-Media Reports and Clippings, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Occoquan Marker, 1979 - 1982 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Occoquan Marker-Photos and Texts-Ceremony and History, 1982 - 1983 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    Photographs
  - Occoquan Marker-Joe Flackne, 1974 - 1987 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Occoquan Marker-Information on Suffragists, 1982 - 1983 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Occoquan Marker-Documentation of Dedication Speeches/Correspondence/Booklet Quotes, 1983 - 1987 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Occoquan Workhouse, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Occoquan Marker Rededication, 2000-2006 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - "Of Swamps, Bogs, and Billabongs", Undated (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Organization, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Organization-Long Range Plan, 1984 - 1988 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Packet Developed for a Finance Workshop, 1988 - 1989 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Preparing League Testimony on FY 1987 County Proposed Budget, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Proclaimations and Awards for LWV of Fairfax, 1969 - 1977 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - P.R. Media Relations Local Coverage, 1990 - 1995 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Program Action Coalitions Local, pre 1991 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Program Action Taken: Local Action Chrono. File, 1995-1998 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Programs Description State "Positions for Action", 1980 - 1989 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Program Planning and Development, 1955-1995 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Publications "Remember the Ladies...", 2001 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Public Relations: Cable TV, 1976 - 1995 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Recycling Guides-Financial Data (Solicitation Sources/Calling Notes), 1989 - 1991 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - 1991 Recycling Guide: Design, Funding, Production, Distribution (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Recycling Guides-History of Awards for and Examples of, 1989-1991 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Regional Govt.-Metropolitan Issues, 1972 - 1982 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Registration Info., 1978 - 1996 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Room and Church Reservations, 1989 - 1996 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Schools, 1970s-1980s (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Schools, 1970s-1980s (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Schools: Action, 1978 - 1991 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Schools: Action, 1978 - 1997 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Schools: Action, 1972 - 1985 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Schools: Budget, 1989 - 1998 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Schools: Committee Activities, 1989 - 1996 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Schools: Family Life Education, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Schools: Performance-Based Pay, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Shaping the Metropolis, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Soil Conservation Award, Undated (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Stagebill: "Promiscuous Rampant Women", 1995 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - State and Local Perception on Candidate Response, 1996 - 1997 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Statements, 1954 - 1965 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Statements Testimony by LWVFA, 1966-1968 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Statements Testimony by LWVFA, 1966-1968 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Sully District Council-Facilities Use, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Super Saturday, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - 1st Year To Use Teachers Super Sat., Sept. 16, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Telephone Tapes, 1977 - 1979 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Telephone Tape Message, 1980 - 1981 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Testimony, 1966-1967 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Testimony, Call to Action, Etc., 1971 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Testimony, Call to Action, Etc., 1971 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Top Land Use Workshop, 1976-1981 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Topic: Schools-Thomas Jefferson Sch. for Science and Technology, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Topic: Schools-Changing Enrollment w/Boundary Changes and Use of Sch. Facilities, 1983 - 1985 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Transportation, 1969 - 1989 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Unit Chair's Handbook, 1990 - 2002 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Unit Chair's Letter, 1996 - 2001 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Units: Unit Formation/Unit Disbanding, 1983 - 1985 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Units: Officers Training, 1977 - 1997 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Units: Officers Unit Chair's Letter, 1988 - 1997 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Unit: Profile Annual Report, 1974 - 1997 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Vienna Day Unit Records, 1993-2002 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Vienna Forum, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Volunteer Registrars, 1981 - 1985 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Voters' Guides, 1991-2004 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Voters' Guide, 1995-1996 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Voters' Guides, 2005 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Voters' Guides (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Voter Guides/Newspaper, 1974-1990 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Voter Guides-Newspaper, 1978 - 1994 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Voters Service Ballot Information, 1980-1982 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Voters Service Booths, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Voter Service Budget Projections, 1996-1997 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Voters Service: Campaign Watch 1992 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - V.S. Candidates Debates [I], 1979 - 1992 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - V.S. Candidates Debates [II], 1965 - 1992 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Voters Service: Citizen Information, 1980 - 1995 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - V.S.: "Choose or Lose" MTV Campaign, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Voters Svc.-Community Outreach, 1979 - 1987 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Voters Service: Debates, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Voters Service: High School Students at Registration, 1989 - 1991 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Voters Service: Hotline Phone Notebook Registration, 1990 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Voters Service: LWVED "Focus on Voters", 1992 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Voters Service Projects, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Voters Service: General Procedure, 1974 - 1996 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Voters Service Making Democracy Work [I], 1998 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Voters Service Making Democracy Work [II], 1998 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Voters Service: National Voter Registration "Take Back the System", 1992 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Voter Service NCA, 1980 - 1984 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Voter Service: Voters Guide/Candidate Questionaire, 1991 - 1995 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Voters Service: Voters Guide Correspondence, 1986 - 1997 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Voters Guide City and Town, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Voters Guide Town and City, 1987-1988 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Voters Guide Town and City, 1987-1988 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - C and T Voters Guide, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Voters Guide Cities and Towns, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Voters Guide, 1990-1991 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Voters Guide: Supervisors, 1991 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Voters Guide-House of Delegates, 1991 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Voters Guide-Senate #2, 1991 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Voter Registration, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 9)